A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Administration and Officers Files, Office Files of Lonnie Sherrod FA1792
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council records, Administration and Officers Files, Office Files of Lonnie Sherrod
1960-1987
Rockefeller Archive Center
Sherrod, Lonnie R. (1950)
Social Science Research Council
FA1792
24.57 Cubic Feet 64 boxes (48 letter document storage boxes, 13 legal document storage boxes, 2 35mm microfilm boxes, and 1 half letter document storage box)
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of administrative files, research materials, grant applications, publications, and reports created and received by Lonnie Sherrod in his role as a Social Science Research Council (SSRC) staff liaison to several SSRC committees. Sherrod was the staff liaison to the following SSRC committees: the Committee on Life-Course Perspective, the Subcommittee on Child Development in Life-Span Perspective, the Committee on Development, Giftedness, and the Learning Process, and the Committee on Biosocial Perspectives on Parental Biology and Offspring Development.
The collection also contains files related to the creation of SSRC publications, including An Inventory of Longitudinal Research on Childhood and Adolescence authored by Frederick Verdonik and Lonnie Sherrod, Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives edited by Aage B. Sørensen, Franz E. Weinert, Lonnie R. Sherrod, and An Inventory of Longitudinal Studies of Middle and Old Age compiled by Susan Migdal, Robald B. Abeles, and Lonnie Sherrod. Some material in the collection relates to Sherrod's role as Treasurer for the Society for the Study of Social Biology (SSSB). The files in Series 1 were created by David Jenness, SSRC Staff Associate assigned to the Committee on Biological Bases of Social Behavior, prior to Sherrod's time at the SSRC.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Collection is arranged in eight series:
1. Committee on Biological Bases of Social Behavior, 1960-1976
2. Subcommittee on Child Development in Life-Span Perspective, 1982-1987
3. Committee on Life-Course Perspectives on Human Development, 1977-1987
4. Committee on Development, Giftedness, and the Learning Process, 1981-1986
5. Inventory of Longitudinal Research on Childhood and Adolescence, 1975-1986
6. Committee on Biosocial Perspectives on Parent Behavior, 1981-1986
7. Administrative Files, 1982-1987
8. Publications, 1964-1987
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records in this collection were received by the Rockefeller Archive Center from the Social Science Research Council in 2016 and 2017.
Child development; Gifted children -- Education -- United States; Human behavior
- Committee on Biological Bases of Social Behavior, 1960-1976; 1; 1.8 Cubic Feet
  Biographical / Historical
  The Social Science Research Council's Committee on Biological Bases of Social Behavior (1966-1979), previously the Committee on Genetics and Behavior (1961-1966), studied the relationship between biology and social science. The committee focused their efforts on understanding how environmental and biological factors impact social class, intelligence, and behavior pathology. One of the committee's most significant projects was a comprehensive survey of the relevant research and policy questions concerning the scholastic achievements and intelligence of children of different races.
  The committee sponsored summer training institutes over a 10-year period to provide training in biology, behavior genetics, population genetics, neurobiology, and psychophysiology to early career social scientists. Through conferences and workshops on topics in the same areas (population biology, neurobiology, and psychophysiology), the committee encouraged research examining the contributions of genetics to the study of social behavior.
  Scope and Contents
  The files in this series were created by David Jenness, SSRC Staff Associate assigned to the Committee on Biological Bases of Social Behavior. They were inventoried as part of Lonnie Sherrod's office files.
  - Summer Training Institute on Neurobiology for Social Scientists Forms and Information Sheets, 1964-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Committee Reports, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Neuroendocrinology, Richard E. Whalen, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Summer Training Institute, Institute for Behavioral Genetic, University of Colorado, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Behavioral and Biological Issues in the Learning Paradigm/Learning Definition Workshop, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - National Institute of Mental Health Grant - Summer Training Institute on Neurobiology for Social Scientists, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Grant Applications, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 401)
  - Proposed Summer Training Institute, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Summer Training Institute on Population Genetics for Social Scientists, Institute for Behavioral Genetics, University of Colorado, Boulder, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - National Institute on Mental Health, Public Health Service - Information, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stress, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Energy Flow Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Man in the Ecosystem: Proceedings of a Conference in Anapolis, Maryland, International Biological Program, 1973 October (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Human Ecology, 1971-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Differential Reproduction in Individuals with Mental and Physical Disorders, Irving I Gottesman and L. Erlenmeyer-Kimling, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Biofeedback Research Society, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Psychiatry, Mental Health, Anthropology Articles, 1962-1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Biological Bases of Reading Disorders, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Society for Neuroscience Roster, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Biomedical and Behavioral Research Reports and Articles, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Neurobiology, 1970-1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Summer Training Institute in Psychophysiology for Social Scientists, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Conference on Genetics, Evolution, and Human Behavior Proposal, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Computer Simulation in Human Population Studies, Bennett Dyke, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Response to David Shapiro's Psychophysiology Proposal, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Intelligence and Genetics, 1966-1973 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Behavior and Fertility, 1960-1973 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
  - Behavioral Biology, Ethology, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - International Meeting Planning, Nutrition Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 29-30)
- Subcommittee on Child Development in Life-Span Perspective, 1982-1987; 2; 6.52 Cubic Feet 9 legal document boxes and 6 letter document boxes
  The Social Science Research Council's Subcommittee on Child Development in Life-Span Perspective (1981-1986) was created as a subcommittee of the SSRC's Committee on Life-Course Perspectives on Human Development (see Series 3). The subcommittee was supported by funding from the Foundation for Child Development. The subcommittee sponsored conferences, workshops, and a summer institute for early career social scientists at the Center for the Advanced Study of Behavioral Sciences. In 1984, the subcommittee published an Inventory of Longitudinal Research on Childhood and Adolescence compiled by Frederick Verdonik and Lonnie Sherrod. The working files of the inventory are housed in Series 5.
  This series contains meeting, conference, and workshop files, planning materials related to subcommittee publications, and correspondence related to the life-course longitudinal research archive later housed at the Henry A. Murray Research Center of Radcliffe College.
  - Adolescence Project Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Adolescence Meeting, 1987 February (Box 4, Folder 34-35)
  - Adolescence Papers, Anne Petersen, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Brain Behavior and Development Genetics, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Transitions in Adolescence Proposal, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
  - Precursors of Adolescence Workshop Material, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Designing Interventions to Reduce Unintended, School-Age Pregnancies, Joel Cohen Statement, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 41-42)
  - Adolescence Materials Sent to Ruby Takanishi, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Preliminary Planning - Teen Pregnancy, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Contracts for Child Development and Life Span Perspective, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Child Development in Life-Span Perspective Volume Final Drafts, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Child Development in Life-Span Perspective - Final Volume - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Brain and Behavior Volume Papers, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 48-50)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Brain-Behavior Interaction During Human Development Conference Grant, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Brain and Behavior Volume - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Child Development in Life-Span Perspective Conference - Woods Hole, Massachusetts - 1986 Meeting Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Schools and Intellectual Development Fall 1986 Workshop, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    Includes Harold Stevenson's research on schooling in Peru
  - Child Development, Life-Span Perspective Papers, 1986 September 15 (Box 8, Folder 67-68, Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Child Development in Life-Span Perspective June 1986 Conference, Woods Hole, Massachusetts - Notes (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Bibliography Cards, undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Conference on Literacy and Schooling; Intellectual Development, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Inventory of Longitudinal Research Archive - Correspondence with Anne Colby, Radcliffe College, Henry A. Murray Research Center, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Inventory of Longitudinal Research Archive - Correspondence with Coordination Committee, European Science Foundation, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Inventory on Longitudinal Child Development Research Correspondence with Researchers - Volume II Studies, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Harold Stevenson Peru Study Materials, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Social-Historical Perspectives on Child Development, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Foundation for Child Development - Subcommittee on Child Development in Life-Span Perspective - Year 4 Grant Report, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Selfhood Conference Notes and Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 80-81)
  - Conference on the Study of Expertise as a Model for Life-Span Cognitive Development, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Conference on Intellectual Development and the Schools, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Conference on Child Development in Life-Span Perspective - Planning and Information for Participants, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 84-85)
  - Letters to New Members, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 242)
  - December 1984 Meeting on "Expertise", 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 283)
  - Toronto Meeting, Society for Research in Child Development (SRCD), 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 284)
  - Minutes of Toronto Meeting, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 285)
  - Precursors of Adolescence Workshop, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 291, Box 39, Folder 292)
  - Workshop on History and Child Development, 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 293)
  - Attributions Workshop Correspondence, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 294)
  - March 6 Planning Meeting, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 295)
  - Conference Volume on Subcommittee on Child Development in Life-Span Perspective, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 296)
  - Intellectual Development and Schools, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 297)
  - General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 302)
  - Precursors of Adolescence Workshop, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 406)
  - Summer Institute on Human Development Memo, undated; 8" floppy disk (Box 64)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
- Committee on Life-Course Perspectives on Human Development, 1977-1987; 3; 10.04 Cubic Feet 19 letter document boxes and 6 legal document boxes
  The Social Science Research Council's Committee on Life-Course Perspectives on Human Development (originally called the Committee on Life-Course Perspective on Middle and Old Age) was active from 1977-1987. The committee's original mandate was to gain a deeper understanding of middle and old age by employing a life-course perspective and working directly with selected ongoing longitudinal and historical studies. By 1982, the committee focused on life-course research beyond middle and old age. The Committee sponsored workshops, conferences, and publications to facilitate life-course research. The committee received funding from the Charles A. Dana Foundation and the Volkswagen Foundation. In 1981, the Subcommittee on Child Development in Life-Span Perspective was created as a subcommittee of the SSRC's Committee on Life-Course Perspectives on Human Development (see Series 2).
  The series contains correspondence, papers, grant reports to the Charles A. Dana Foundation, research planning materials, conference and meeting files, chapters from Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives edited by Aage B. Sørensen, Franz E. Weinert,and Lonnie R. Sherrod published by Psychology Press in 1986, grant reports to the Volkswagen Foundation, and requests related to An Inventory of Longitudinal Studies of Middle and Old Age by Susan Migdal, Ronald P. Abele, and Lonnie Sherrod published by the Social Science Research Council in 1981.
  - Notes and Correspondence, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Aging in the Context of the Life-Course: Suggestions for Further Research - Report to the Charles A. Dana Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Committee Notes, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Charles A. Dana Foundation 1984 Grant - Life-Course Program Reports, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Charles A. Dana Foundation - Social Structure and Aging Final Report, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Charles A. Dana Foundation - Life-Course Perspective 1986 Meeting Notes (Box 8, Folder 59-61)
  - Charles A. Dana Foundation - Life-Course Perspective - Social Structure and Aging Processes January Meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Charles A. Dana Foundation - Social Structure and Aging Processes - Fall 1984 Meeting, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 63-65)
  - Charles A. Dana Foundation - Life-Course Perspective, Health, and Aging - Spring 1984, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Life-Course Perspectives on Human Development, Subcommittee on Social Structure and the Aging Process Planning Meeting, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Research Planning - Peak Potentials in Performance, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 216)
  - Research Planning - General, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 217)
  - Neurobiology and Psychiatric Disorder - Planning Meeting, David Glass, David Cohen, and Fritz Henn, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 218)
  - Committee on Cognitive Research - Research Planning - Cognition and the Workplace, Sylvia Scribner, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 219)
  - Research Planning - Conceptions of Risk, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 220)
  - Spencer Foundation Inquiry - Predoctoral Fellowship Competition, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 221)
  - Research Planning - The Family, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 222)
  - Life Span Volume - Foundation Funding, Program Topics, Etc., 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 223)
  - Violence, Values, and Moral Development - Drafts, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 224)
    "Prejudice, Ethnocentrism, and Violence in an Age of High Technology," David Hamburg
  - Teen Pregnancy - 1986 Memo Response - Chapters and Articles, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 231-232)
  - Teen Pregnancy - Joel Cohen Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 233-234)
  - Letters to New Co-Chairs and Members, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 239)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Martin, Chapter II, New Figure 2, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 243)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Finn, Chapter II.2 Figures, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 244)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Carl-Gerhard Gottfries, Chapter II.3 Figures, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 245)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Vogel, Chapter II.4 Figures, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 246)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Bergmen and Looper Chapter II.5 Figures, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 247)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Featherman Chapter II.6 Figures, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 248)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Riley Chapter III.1 Figure, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 249)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Elder et al., Chapter III.7 Figures, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 250)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Seligman, Chapter IV.3. - Figures, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 251)
  - Human Development and the Life Course: Multidisciplinary Perspectives, Sorensen, Weinert, and Sherrod - Heckhausen, Chapter IV.4 Figures, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 252)
  - Arthur E. Imhof - Life-course Patterns of Women and Their Husbands: 16th to 20th Century - Figures, undated (Box 33, Folder 253)
  - Figure from Aage Sorensen and Martin Seligman - Life-Span Influences in the Process of Learned Helplessness, undated (Box 33, Folder 254)
  - Bill Damon and Anne Colby - Workshop on Moral Exemplar Project, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 256)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 257)
  - Parenting Across the Life Span Papers, 1983-1986 (Box 33, Folder 258)
  - The Advisory and Planning Committee on Social Indicators, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 259)
  - National Statistics on Social Conditions and Change: A Research Agenda for the 1980s, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 260)
  - Children in Their Contexts: A Goodness-of-Fit Model - Draft, Richard M. Lerner and Jacqueline V. Lerner, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 261)
  - A Biosocial Perspective on Paternal Behavior and Involvement, Michael E. Lamb, Joseph H. Pleck, Eric L. Charnov, and James A. Levine, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 262)
  - Conference on Biosocial Life Span Approaches to Parenting and Offspring Development - Papers, 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 264-266)
  - Grants Program for Public Policy Research on Contemporary Hispanic Studies - Application Guidelines and Checklist, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 273)
  - Committee on Life-Course Perspectives - Final Report Volkswagen, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 299)
  - Volkswagen Foundation Materials, 1983-1985 (Box 39, Folder 300)
  - The Psychology of Control and Aging, Margret M. Baltes and Paul B. Baltes, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 307)
  - Committee Correspondence and Circulated Papers, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 308)
  - Social Structure and Aging - Planning Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 309)
  - Summer Institute on Cognition-Emotion Interrelationships, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 318)
  - 1984 Postdoctoral Summer Institute - Individual Development and Social Change - Summary Document and Agenda (Box 42, Folder 319)
  - Bibliography (Papers), 1978-1983 (Box 43, Folder 329-330, Box 44, Folder 331-336, Box 45, Folder 337-342, Box 46, Folder 343-346, Box 47, Folder 347-350, Box 48, Folder 351)
    Arrangement
    Papers are arranged alphabetically by authors' last name
  - Life-Course Perspectives on Middle and Old Age - Bibliography, 1977-1980 (Box 48, Folder 352)
  - The Employment Decision of Married Mothers of Infants, Paul Smith Avioli, undated (Box 48, Folder 353)
  - Plasticity of Behavioral Development Through the Life Span: Promise of Despair? - Outline, Paul B. Baltes, 1979 January (Box 48, Folder 354)
  - Heidelberg Business Meeting Minutes Draft, 1981 April 25-26 (Box 49, Folder 361)
  - Heidelberg Meeting - Lonnie Sherrod's Notes and Correspondence, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 362)
  - International Conference on Life-Course Research on Human Development, Berlin - Papers, 1982 September 16-21 (Box 49, Folder 364, Box 50, Folder 365)
  - International Conference on Life-Course Research on Human Development, Berlin - Conference Volume, 1982-1984 (Box 50, Folder 366-367)
  - Social Structure and Aging: Followup and Planning Meeting, Summer, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 368)
  - Social Structure and Aging Process Planning Meeting - Lonnie Sherrod's Notes, 1983 May 5 (Box 50, Folder 369)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 370)
  - National Institute on Aging - Aging Research, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 371)
  - Berlin Conference Correspondence, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 372-373)
  - Berlin Conference Vouchers, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 374)
  - Business Meeting, 1982 September (Box 51, Folder 375)
  - Berlin Conference - Lonnie Sherrod's Notes, 1983 September (Box 51, Folder 376)
  - Committee on Life-Course Perspective, Subcommittee on Middle and Old Age, Spring, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 377)
  - Committee Program Plans March 7, 1982 Meeting (Box 52, Folder 378)
  - Planning Meeting - May 1, 1983 New York City (Box 52, Folder 379-380)
  - Berlin Volume - Correspondence, Suggested Edits, and Drafts, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 381)
  - Berlin Chapter - Epilogue: Retrospective and Prospective Views of Life-Course Research on Human Development, Lonnie Sherrod and Orville Brim - Comments, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 382)
  - National Institute on Aging (NIA) Grant, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 383)
  - Planning Meeting - Business Minutes, 1980 July-August (Box 53, Folder 384)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 385)
  - Workshop and Subcommittee Proposals, 1981-1983 (Box 53, Folder 386)
  - An Inventory of Longitudinal Studies of Middle and Old Age, 1981-1983 (Box 60, Folder 413)
  - An Inventory of Longitudinal Studies of Middle and Old Age - Requests, 1983-1985 (Box 60, Folder 414)
  - Life-Course Committee Materials Sent Out, 1981-1983 (Box 60, Folder 416)
- Committee on Development, Giftedness, and the Learning Process, 1981-1986; 4; 3.31 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
  The Social Science Research Council's Committee on Development, Giftedness, and the Learning Process (1980-1990) was created following the conclusion of the Committee on Gifted Children (1975-1980). The Committee was tasked with exploring the concept of giftedness, the identification of the gifted individual, and educational provisions for gifted individuals. The Committee studied the nature and conditions of exceptional performance within domains such as art, music, and science. That committee's initial activities were supported by the American Psychological Foundation with funds from the estate of Esther Katz Rosen and later received funding from the Mellon Foundation.
  The series contains materials related to committee funding from the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, correspondence, and meeting and workshop files.
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation - Final Report of the SSRC Committee on Development, Giftedness, and the Learning Process, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 213)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1984 March-April (Box 30, Folder 214)